wrappixel.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Wrappixel

__Menu __Close Menu

__Menu

##### Login to WrapPixel ×

You can Login with your Facebook or Google   
Account as well.

By Sign In or Signup to WrapPixel.com using Facebook, Google or our login/register form, You are agreeing to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy (GDPR ).

  *  __ WrapPixel does not share any personal information with anyone. We do not sell / rent / lease your personal information to anyone / third party. We do not sell / rent / lease or provide outside access to our mailing list or any personal data we store.
  *  __ Any data that user stores via our login / registration facilities is fully owned by that user or business. At any time a user or business is free to take their data and leave by simply deleting their account from our site / facilities.
  *  __ WrapPixel only collects such personal information that is necessary for you to access and use our website services. This personal information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, email address.
  *  __ We do collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual or business concerned.
  *  __ We protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  *  __ We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
  *  __ We may use personal information in manner that does not identify you specifically nor allow you to be contacted but to show number of registered users, number of unique visitors and the most frequently pages visited.
  *  __ We can change the price of our templates anytime without any prior notification or mentioning it anywhere on our site or blog.
  *  __ We can remove any template from our site anytime.
  *  __ We can delete the fraud account with name or email – “test” – “123…” , and you can’t complain us for that. so use your original email and name. 
  * __ In terms of Free template download means you have to share via twitter or Facebook to get it.
  *  __ If we do change our privacy policy, it will be updated here and you will be informed by email.
